affiliatedproductnetwork.com 2008-12-17

# Affiliated Product Network : Learn, Earn, Travel, Protect, Support and Advertise

**APN PRIVACY STATEMENT**

**Completing the Sign-up and Profile**  
APN will not sell, share, or rent personal information to any 3rd. party. It is necessary that an APN Affiliate must complete their profile with complete, accurate and verifiable information. APN does not require your date of birth, social security number, identification number, passport information or drivers license number. The information requested is necessary for effective communication with the APN Affiliate. 

**Site Security**  
APN takes every precaution to protect our affiliate’s personal information. Information submitted via our site, is protected to our best efforts and is only accessible to our administration staff. Should the APN security become breached in any way the APN Affiliate agrees to hold APN harmless for any and all damages as a result of any breach. 

**Updating or Correcting Personal Information**  
An APN Affiliate may correct or update personal information in the restricted affiliate back-office. 

**Communicating With An APN Affiliate**  
APN will communicate with the affiliates to provide any information, marketing material, issues relating to accounts, site updates, and service announcements via email. This information may also be posted within the APN Affiliates Back-office. 

**Notification of Changes in This Privacy Policy**  
Any changes regarding our Privacy Policy will be communicated via email. An APN Affiliate may notify APN if they do not agree to APN’s change or intent to use this information in a manner other than as stated in this statement.
